been a day you watched any of my last
things that I posted today I posted a
road map just a story that I wrote a
long time ago a year and a half ago and
then I had this event row necklace broke
and it means a lot because of who came
from and what that means and all of the
coincidences and or universal guides one
of which is the person whose birthday it
is his necklace as I talked about in
maybe the video I posted I've worked a
couple of wasn't the sound that he spoke
thought and had an addiction and it was
happening well I was looking with a
minimum for being judgmental about him
up on it and there was something about
me following the signs to Papa so I
totally simple and in so doing was
sitting here recording myself on the
other place what I do or it's never
going live and part of what I'm here to
showcase is this is this process and the
more willing I am to just showcase the
process because recording it explaining
it after the fact it doesn't look as
well and so I was even here plugging
that way by Facebook is basically what I
was doing so also the person I was
talking about whose video I was watching
out in the dead Jubilee with a necklace
broke and all that happened previously
on there was
I was able to follow a train up up
that's what happened previously
previously on oh I remember
Zach Geist who was speaking but
potentially was or commented I comments
like three times off the video because I
was asking you questions and then I just
did my one-off hey I'm here to save the
world come watch come have fun it's just
true like that's the point this I keep
talking about this like I have this
thing inside of me and you just trust me
when I get that that's never gonna be
the case people are just gonna come on
bore it with something that doesn't
entice them and it's about me finding
that piece well being as transparent
about how I'm doing this process the
whole thing all of it my full human self
that is capable of coming up with us it
is on the journey to create it and is it
imperfect human being who needs to be
allowed to be imperfect in order to
create what I am here to create and I'm
talking weird through the first person
and that that is what we're here to
create and so this is what I can't do it
if I'm explaining it I shouldn't be
explaining it I should just be doing it
I just can't give you a picture what's
inside my head so I was talking about
that the companies that are owned by
people who are very rich and might not
want us to create the tech quantitive if
they know what is truly in it for them
they would want us to because they too
have
loved ones in themselves they get cancer
and die and it suffer from addiction and
have a lot of things happen the wealth
does not shield you from including you
know needing to drink clean water and
bring clean air and eat clean food can
optimize your health and optimizing your
health is directly related to how much
you optimize everybody else's health
your abundance is directly related all
of the abundance you give everybody else
not in some hokey I don't know I believe
in karma but like I get why other people
wouldn't but in a way it's just
mathematical that's the more we live in
flow and the more we give and the more
we enjoy that process so it's you don't
need to compensate me for it the more
there is of that out there in the world
and that is a powerful force when we tap
into that in any way shape or form like
a tiny fraction when we allow humanity
to give the passion to acknowledge that
what they're dying burning to give to
the rest they want hope they want
something that they can actually do and
feel like it's gonna have an effect in
the world and we don't want to give up a
lot you don't want to sacrifice what we
have for something we don't know and
working within who we are as voters as
consumers as people that are individual
in a huge big system how can we make the
best decisions how can we recreate it so
that we trust it so that it functions
and is efficient so that it benefits
everybody
not a perfect system better for us than
we have now and we get to participate in
the creation of it to make it better we
get to participate not just in voting
for representatives but in actually
creating the solutions in finding holes
in the solutions in collecting the data
and the information that is necessary
for it and unless you are doing that
full-time and we figure out how you are
not paid for it you were doing it
because you want to you enjoy the thing
you were doing and you were creating in
a way because you're given the tools in
the system but other people have created
because it's their flow and their
passion to be able to do what you want
and need and have access to systems that
get all of our needs met because we've
unleashed Humanity on humanity's
problems and that's the only way to do
it
like we're on this planet with our given
current diversity so that we can solve
this problem so that we can solve our
own problems and a lot of our own
problems don't get solved as individuals
there is no singular cure for cancer
you might luck out and find one you
can't reproduce that for your loved ones
together we can cure cancer together we
can create an efficient system where our
needs are met and most of our wants and
will not destroyed our planet to do it
where everybody has abundance we don't
need everybody to agree to start doing
that to start doing that we can just
start doing that we can
to come together as to as for as a
million with systems that are designed
for that process because it's gonna not
work and then we're gonna figure out
what systems we need and then we're
gonna create them and then we're gonna
improve them we're just gonna keep we're
gonna use what we currently have
we're gonna keep improving and creating
better this is what I am here to create
because when my needs are met when I'm
able to live my life on my own terms and
do what I enjoy and what is easy my mind
creates a world that works for everyone
with technology where everyone has
abundance because that's what my mind
does that's what I was put here to do I
don't know how or why I have my own
sense making around that but it's doing
it so who cares why I need to
find a way to utilize it for the greater
good because that's what it wants to do
it doesn't want to create it for my own
personal wealth assumed all what this is
designed for that is the broken thing
that it is fixing and I am the broken
thing that it is fixing it is where I
lack that I can find solutions in
society that would fix that problem that
I cannot create them myself I can't I'll
follow a recipe and manage to get I'm
getting better but like there's some
executive functioning things do not work
for my brain and yet it will create
entire systems for like well we can all
fix it this way and it's not that it's a
fully made out yes it can roll out
tomorrow it would roll out tomorrow but
it's how we create those and how we walk
through a process of tapping into the
flow of each
and feed them the tools to say what's
working and not working and co-creating
solutions that work for them and then we
all get the solutions they create and
infinitum
just like exponentially grows the more
people we bring on board the more ideas
they bring on board the more finances
they bring on board the more data they
bring to the table
they bring themselves to the table all
anyone else has is money and customers
there is no way they can compete with
joyful passionate flow labor that is
creating innovation and paying people
that are doing the physical like that
are creating this stuff and working
full-time a living amazing wage and
we're creating a life that works for
everyone not just our employees not just
the people who are directly related in
the labor to run this but all of the
labor that like entertains us and what
we want human beings doing is what calls
to their soul it's like what they would
enjoy doing what is both easy a
combination if it being easy for them as
an individual and challenging for them
as an individual and finding it's a
personal choice we are all on our own
individual journey and figuring that out
how we co-create that together how you
allow people to be on their own journey
cuz ya can't really judge it you can
barely judge your own let alone anybody
else's you have to find the way where we
can come together and doing what is
currently not working isn't working so
we need to find something new and we
need to test new things and we need to
be able to see what is happening when we
Tet when we create them in the world and
have for thought and see if we can
mitigate risk forever
releasing things see what happens as
things we could never foresee happen or
things are such a little probability and
they actually happen what do we do we
can solve it all together and it's the
only way we solve it we cannot solve it
for profit we cannot solve it in
isolation and we cannot solve it in
microcosms in competition with one
another we can absolutely be autonomous
human selves that do what brings us joy
and form groups that bring us connection
that we want to be with and we can
co-create together the tools that needed
to do that but the efficiency the global
peace the peace were we're all putting
it into the giant heap in this format
that solves it all has to be global it
has to be owned by all of us it has to
be something beyond borders and culture
and therefore we have to know a simple
way of getting along well enough to do
it our leaders might never get along how
do we get along how do we find what and
it's this is how simple it is oh we
don't its spoiler alert we don't all get
along we find people that we get along
with and then we freak the out on
each other and then or whatever is our
version is we hide we run we do you know
we we act like a human who's been
wounded and then we grow do that a
little tiny bit less and repeat the
process like that is how we grow when we
shame when we make it people wrong for
who and what they are it makes
everything infinitely worse for
ourselves for society allowing people to
be who they are
assuming good and allowing them to bring
their vessels so the
world is the peace that we can give to
one another and I can't leave without 50
minutes I think I that was I like it it
works I just stopped in here and not
ramble about Who I am I'll ruin it
let's do but it's not cuz it's this
process of three years has been
unlearning an ego and being able to make
an ass of myself like I was also writing
like what that's what I want from people
truly is for them to come and share this
idea part like not actually don't
actually attack it don't like actually
come at me with legal stuff and things
but the verbal part but I like come see
what won't work about it beyond just
like right human nature like right this
isn't designed for everyone to get on
board it's designed for incremental
growth that is an attractor it brings
people in because you were offering both
hope a system of change that they get to
participate directly in because we're
literally asking what would you like to
do to participate and how do we make
that possible and how do we create the
tools to make that happen how do we help
you create the tools to make that happen
what do you need to participate what is
it you want to do for the greater good
how do we create those tools and that's
a lot of everything like we start with
simple things or things that make nearly
everyone's life better what are food
apps what are you know financial savings
apps how do we both buy things together
how do we share in tools and
entertainment and and create things that
are maybe not simple ones as we progress
if we like everything we do makes it
infinitely better we help people eat
better well now they have like they have
more time more energy
more health to spend on everything and
anything their family their current job
projects for us and then even if a tiny
bit of that goes back to creating
something new for the rest of us that
pays for it all and it doesn't actually
pay for it we're all paying for it
sharing the cost of it we're making it
much more fair and even or not just burn
up crazy in Utopia
I'm hoping when we look at the world we
create in 10 15 20 years
it looks like utopia from where we are
but you never reach utopia utopia is not
a thing it's a constant making it better
until it's good so it has been a day I
wanted to come out and share that
there's that like process I don't know I
don't know what that just was but I
liked it and so I'm gonna stop this and
no one came on and that was exactly what
was supposed to happen I at one point I
whatever someone came on you too but I
like jumped off as God about me I've had
people and it's fine and I'm used to
people being on because of the FAQ and I
want people on like I want literally
somebody on camera with me you can and
to tear it apart like this is my life
this is what I am here to do so it's
either an idea that needs to be torn
apart to save me in my life or I want
help creating it like something has to
happen because just sitting with it and
being in it without actually having it
come into the world doesn't work and I'm
figuring out how to create it which is
also what the product is it's what I'm
here to do a showcase this is the really
annoying bro so I was reading something
in the world anyone happened know I'll I
was like gonna say anyone have any
advice I want advice I'm so against
advice because it just hinders my honing
her process if
ask someone something if they share
something isn't advice that is just them
sharing their own beam I will get what I
need from it and so figure you know uh
this is just it's a fun process
I'm figuring out who to be like what do
I need and in other people how do I work
with other people to create this because
the level that everyone else seems to
need to be at to do something like this
does not work for me like I need for
personal assistance to figure out how to
do this stuff to deal with like the
people and the executive functioning
logistics I think executive functioning
and certain other things and that is
like we're all human beings that are
like that like we struggle in areas and
we can help each other in the area as we
struggle we also excel in certain areas
and when we're helped with the part we
struggle we can excel even more at those
areas for and with each other creating
the tools together creating a world that
works and functions gives us game B and
so what I want is the group I want what
I would love is a small group of people
who are willing to have these
conversations on how we create a world
that works for everyone how do you
create a space that works for you what
isn't good in your life that could be
made better or is okay but could be made
better what's stopping you from eating
better like truly not self-help
like yeah it's too expensive and far
away in a Blasi cool how do we bring the
food to you how do we figure this is
devote how do we motivate you to do it
like how do we actually get the food
good food to you in you if that's
something you want cuz it's not
designing for profit to sell you
something it's how do we help you create
the solutions you want because we all
got a lot of that in common and we can
co-create those solutions together how
do we figure out our personal goals how
do we combine raised
versus to make it easier to find a
teacher hire a coach together do get a
venue find what venues work in the city
like all of the informations just out
there floating around we can organize
the out and use that data actually
she's quite easier lives that then we
can put in if we don't like all these
things out there like grammarly
requiring that you have perfect grammar
and and having a calendar so you know
exactly where you're supposed to be in
supposed to like they don't they help
some people they don't help everyone
because they're not accessible and they
don't I'm trying to say like we require
people to have them then that becomes
the bar and if you don't have them and
everyone else has all of these gadgets
you look stupid and you look lazy and
you look and it's unless our
user-friendly free and you're able to
say this is not working for me can we
fix this we make this work which is what
we need to do we cannot make
technological solutions for our
population that our population doesn't
understand we already are at a height of
distrust and a height of things breaking
down as questioning authority and
authority actually breaking down that we
like our currency system is complex and
people don't understand it but it used
to be simple and it used to be something
that people just exchanged easily and it
was like is easy to understand and you
seem to know how to count then there was
a counting and interest and ends crazy
ridiculous loans that are bad and we
became and it became complex and now
people don't understand that money is
dead and then it's not on the gold
reserve and that all it's just not good
it's not good our buddies created it's
all just a big Ponzi scheme
and I took my my point of that was after
when she does know that no that was not
quite enough oh well
it was meant to come back oh that was
the point the cryptocurrency is a cool
concept and the truth is if there's ever
a currency that we all get behind it
becomes the currency that's what
currency is is something we all agreed
to but when it's too complex for people
to understand and it's new people aren't
going to adopt it in the same way as if
it's one we co-create together with the
best features that we understand and
then some we don't understand we're like
oh that's what that does when blockchain
technology can have a lot of it's
amazing implication applications if we
own it together if it's something that
we can understand together meaning that
if you want to understand it there's a
way to understand it it's not too
complex for average people or at least
they can see the path and see that other
people who understand it and are able to
communicate it in a way that they kind
of understand but they truly understand
and they're voting yes they're saying
yes this is it this is this is that they
can more trust it because it's it's not
just in understanding it some of us we
will need to understand exactly how it
works to trust it other people can trust
an expert can trust somebody else to say
yes this versus doesn't but they still
need not transparency that this is why I
trust this person or don't trust this
person this and here's their record for
things they've they've known in the past
and I'm rambling and when I would have
nowhere so I am going to probably not be
stoned when doing this but I am going to
try to come on more often to showcase
this pros
just ether ranting about what we can
create together or the next idea as I
mentioned
this all started I was like I mean just
by facebook it's like Facebook could
just give itself over to the people if
they really cuz they also we get to cure
cancer we get to anyone who'd like any
human being who truly sees the potential
what we can co-create together wants
access to that because they get better
they get their best life out of it like
that's what you get is your best life
out of working with everyone else and
giving them their best life and like but
I think it more than I do
if their best life is more than you do
and yeah they get more than you do up
your game get a better life like it
isn't about who has the biggest house
and who drives the fastest car it's
about what makes you happy what do you
want to be doing who do you want to be
doing it with what experiences and
people do want to be surrounded with
there is no better than that like I
think it's just certain go surf right
cool
you gotta go can't be think Oakham
peeing there is no competition in living
your best life you get to choose wait do
I like campaign is it something I
actually enjoy or no is it something I'm
doing because I'm supposed to like
camping or is it actually something
that's going to refresh me challenge me
something I enjoy because if it is yeah
do camping and do it on Pinterest and do
it but don't do it for Pinterest like
pick what you're here to do and the more
we do that the more I'm doing I'm doing
that that's just like what I'm doing I'm
living as me and I will find people who
are okay with me and I want to co-create
this and we will figure out amongst us
what that looks like but it kind of
looks like it's what I'm looking for
live on camera is solder the best to
meet weekly for an hour with people
watching because I think that'd be
really fun or weird
talking about the pieces brainstorming
basically having a staff meeting on on
camera and if that sounds super boring
might absolutely be we it's not about
the audience being entertained it's
about us having a record of it being
transparent and figuring out a way to
enjoy the process which means having fun
which we need you know saying what works
so it doesn't work figuring out how to
make it easy and fun for us to co-create
this and the more we're able to be in
that space to do that more people are
going to want to watch and participate
because it's not just about us having
conversations and it's making decisions
there are things we need help with and
the more people there are the more
faster we can create this because it's
also to the audience what is it working
what do you want to create in the world
how do we help you concrete that how do
we not have these live on YouTube but we
do more of an idea cafe and create
rounds of questions on unzoom or other
existing technology and breaking out and
having the smaller conversations and how
do we bring that up to a bigger group so
it's effective and when those questions
arise we need a system to be able to
upload them to say yes that's an
important question that's one we should
address right away and part of that is
having questions about the system of
communication itself and having
conversations test it we enjoy and what
we want to talk about what do we want to
what we want to talk about let's we have
the system of communication of how to
communicate is larger group like if
10,000 people can work together on a
project successfully because there's a
core group of people doing it on camera
that are like the board of directors a
larger group who are not on camera
whether they cheat because they choose
not to be who are doing the physical
work making the tech doing the graphics
doing that piece of it
and if they want can absolutely be on
camera but if they're not you know don't
want to sit there but the board's hiring
them to do the work the greater group is
the ones actually helping envision what
this
group is creating and these people are
in charge of creating it like actually
bring it how do we get these people to
have their ideas given in an effective
way to these people so they can
co-create it and how do we facilitate
that process how do we serve that
process and the first two circles are
paid for it and the other circles that
are just doing voting and just doing
commute like when you come on the idea
cafe you weren't paid to come on the
idea cafe you were hopefully having an
enjoyable conversation that is payment
in and of itself that is what we are
creating that is the social media
platform we will be creating with idea
Cafe is one where people can have your
real authentic conversation and have
connection with one or more other human
beings and can do that as often as much
as they want and if what we create isn't
fun if it isn't simple if people don't
want to come back how do we help you
that like you're part of the process
tell us what would make it better
because we want to create it for you me
I know how to create it for me kind of
I'm working on it if we work together we
know how to create it together and again
I've said this so many times but I'm
going oh no I can do this all night it's
late and it's been a day an amazing day
at a hard day a challenging day and I'm
still waking 11:30 it's just kind of
like when I first put the necklace on
surge in energy the more I follow this
path the more energy I have I found it
found that it's like my it's all its
intertwined and you guys get to watch it
all because I'm gonna showcase it off I
wasn't because I get that I'm gonna look
crazy this whole process is gonna look
ridiculous
but like what does crazy mean just me
it's not normal
and yeah it is gonna look like that
because it is that we are gonna do
something different because what we've
been doing isn't working we are to try
radical acceptance I'm doing that by
radically accepting me and then finding
other people who are willing to be on
that journey themselves and as a group
and what we are creating are the tools
to help more and more and more people Oh
fix come onboard and co-create solutions
and tools and it just exponentially gets
bigger have I said enough do people
understand what I'm saying zero people
watch it one day this is gonna cuz
that's the point the point isn't that
this goes viral right now it's not meant
to I'm just supposed to look like an
idiot for a while
showcase this something happens I would
just keep getting the leaves and
eventually you guys are part of this
process I just keep moving on to the
next step and I'm totally open
that's what currently my next step is I
would love to find other people who this
is fun for they want to come on board
and have a conversation like the other
night in the sense-making wormhole
conversation in the game be coffee shop
was awesome I love that conversation it
was like 16 of us and it was just
flowing one person would talk and then
one person would be like well that
brought up and me this and it was like
you weren't talking to talk alone no I
wasn't talking to talk I can I love to
talk to talk I interrupt people I jump
in like I get excited this wasn't that
because it was like the group who is
having a conversation and although I
would still have liked it to be a
smaller groups because I like a more
intimate conversation like 16 people
that's too many people for me I want to
have like a 3/4 person conversation but
I think there can be diversity up too
right you wanna have a conversation if
you people or have it in a way like the
world cafe where you're a hundred people
having a conversation and breaking off
into groups and then coming back and
having a conversation and maybe there's
multiple ones of that going on so that
the hundred people are like coming back
be like wait what did you what
what's yours like if you're conveying it
back to the bigger group because you're
having intimate conversations and
they're all a little bit different and
then the bigger groups having a
conversation and they're a little bit
different and the largest group is
having a conversation that are like oh
this is the common thread where then
they weren't talking to each other they
were in isolation really because these
people were going amongst tables of
themselves and say what these people and
these people and what was it they
created that was in common and wasn't
and the more like the more we just let
people geek out in the area they want to
geek out in like there is nothing on
this planet that somebody isn't
passionate about figuring out every
piece of this is somebody's favorite
thing I got I guarantee you there's all
of the solutions nearly every one of the
problems we have on this planet in
somebody's notebook in their house they
just don't know how to put it out in the
world for an energy crisis you've been
for cancer research and tools to make
you know life more he's he and fun
creating the system that allows people
to do that as person watching I've been
talking to myself for 40 minutes so I'm
about to wrap up here lasting because it
has been a long day then I stopped to
join and came on here and I answered
that question the question in the title
of this one addiction or guide it was
definitely the guy it's the path the GPS
that led me is multiplied by coz I came
on into this and I think I did a fairly
good job of explaining what it is
creating together kinda sorta we'll see
we'll see if anyone watches this and if
it does anything but I'm growing and
learning and I'm showcasing the process
that is the job and I will see you it's
all much more regularly is the idea
take care